# BRITTANY WINSTON

## full stack web developer

https://brittanywinston.3owl.com





b.jazzy.w@gmail.com



706 - 326 - 4408

• https://github.com/castledoor

• https://linkedin.com/in/brittanywinston

I have spent the last five years growing into new disciplines, from architecture to graphic design to web development. I have been teaching myself front-end web design with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, and also back-end development with Ruby and Rails, with the help of the Epicodus web development program I have been able to grow and evolve into a full stack developer. My background as an architect and graphic designer has helped me embrace and understand all aspects of the web development process.

## Experience:

Chick Tech • Portland, Or • Oct-Nov 2013

### Intern Developer

ChickTech is a nonprofit organization dedicated to providing hands-on opportunities for girls and women to get engaged with technology. Our team of 5 is building a customized volunteer management system to increase volunteer engagement and collaboration. The product is mainly built in Ruby on Rails, with jQuery and AJAX to improve usability, and heavily tested using RSpec and Capybara.

Freelance • Atlanta, Ga - Shanghai, China • 2010 - 2013 Graphic Designer

Creating graphic designs and production images for a range of companies varying in specialities and size. Including but not limited to the following

- Neutral Hue http://neutralhue.com/
- Phillips
- Nprove Electronics

Bussola & Ralph • Shanghai, China • March 2013 - July 2013

## Project Manager

Managing high end retail interiors projects from design to installation.

- Designed shop layouts and details
- Quality checked during production and on-site construction
- Cost analysis, quotation, and billing

Vast Design • Shanghai, China • September 2012 - March 2013 Architectural Designer

Specialized in high rise and mixed use buildings, and urban planning

- Concept design
- 3d modeling and presentation
- Graphic designing (marketing materials & client presentations)
- Experience working on large and small scale projects around China

## Education:

- Epicodus web development boot camp Jul Nov 2013
- Southern Polytechnic State University 2008-2012 Bachelor's of Architecture and Design

## Technical Toolbox

#### Front-End

- · Javascript
- $\cdot$ jQuery
- $\cdot AJAX$
- · Ember.is
- ·HTML/CSS/SASS
- · Bootstrap / Foundation

#### Back End

- · Ruby
- · Rails
- ·TDD
- .00
- · APIs

#### Version Control

 $\cdot \, Git$ 

#### Testing

- · Rspec
- · Mocha / Chai
- · Capybara

#### Database

- ·SQL
- · Postgres
- · Active Record

#### Other

- · Pair programming
- Adobe Creative Suite 4-6